{
    "id": "b2658c56fe4d4de8aa6f786bcf17431d",
    "title": "Infinitive With Or Without To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Let him ………………. what he wants to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "to do"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He didn’t allow me ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ……………….. things out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sort",
                "to sort"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ought ……………….. the instructions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "follow",
                "to follow"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was unable …………………. over the grief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "to get"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He made me …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "to wait"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was made ………………… the whole story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repeat",
                "to repeat"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard him …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sing",
                "to sing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I bade him ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I forgot ………………… the letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "post",
                "to post"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}